特大新闻 大家注意啦
Great news, everybody!
今年是头一年 感恩节我休息
This year for once, I don't have to work on Thanksgiving.
我们终于可以全家团圆了
So we can all be together!
我还可以做感恩节晚宴
And I can cook Thanksgiving dinner.
-好吧 -耶
- All right. - Yay.
拜托 这是怎么回事
Okay, what happened there?
亲爱的 别这样 我们只是感觉
Honey, come on, it's just that cooking
做感恩节晚宴太费事了
Thanksgiving dinner is a lot of work.
是啊 难道出去下馆子不好吗
Yeah, are you sure we shouldn't just eat out?
我的意思是 这都是为了您好
I mean, for your sake.
没门儿
No way.
每年的感恩节我都只能吃医院外面
Every Thanksgiving I have to eat Turkey sandwiches.
自动售货机里的火鸡三明治
Out of the hospital vending machine.
而你们也只能去吃老时光自助餐
And you guys have to go to the old time buffet.
今年我们团聚了
This year we're gonna be together,
而且我要亲自下厨
And I am gonna cook.
老时光自助餐好吃不贵
Old time buffet offers quality and value.
没错 而且那里的炸鸡柳 那叫一个香
Yeah, and their chicken fingers, mwah!
对吧
Right?
我们在家吃 已成定局
We are having dinner here and that is final.
好吧 就依你
All right, okay.
事实上呢 和你们说吧 我有个事情要宣布下
Actually, you know, I have a Thanksgiving announcement.
今年爷爷和咱们一起过节
This year we are going to be joined by grandpa.
是邓肯爷爷
Grandpa Duncan.
耶
Yeah.
伤心了吧
Hurts, doesn't it?
噢 别这样啊 大家
Oh, come on, you guys.
-我老爸也并不是一无是处 -比如呢
- My dad has some good qualities. - Such as?
比如 他呼出的二氧化碳 正是植物所需要的
You know what? He exhales carbon dioxide, which is needed by plants.
成了 听着 情况越来越糟
All right, well, we've got bigger problems.
还是让老妈来做感恩节晚宴吧
Mom's cooking Thanksgiving dinner.
噢 不不不不不
Oh, no no no no no.
本宅金牌大厨
The best chef in the house...
PJ下厨来做感恩节晚宴
P.J. Is cooking Thanksgiving dinner.
我吗 老妈是不会同意的
I am? She's never gonna let me.
所以你要用瞒天过海之计
That's why you have to trick her.
给她制造一种她在做饭的错觉 而实际上
Give her the illusion that she's cooking, when in reality,
你才是那个掌勺的人
You're the one doing all the work.
明白了 明白了 只有一个疑问
Got it, got it. Just one question.
制造什么错觉
What does illusion mean?
三个词
Three words...
做 感恩节 晚宴
Cook Thanksgiving dinner.
现在做吗
Right now?
放松 老爸 我和你开玩笑呢
Relax, dad. Just messing with you.
噢 对了 感恩节 是两个词
Oh, by the way, thanksgiving... two words.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
校订： line
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z liloelva
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第二十九集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E29  It's a Charlie Duncan Thanksgiving
你在画什么呢 查莉
What you drawing there, Charlie?
火鸡
A Turkey.
-是吗 -是啊
- Are you sure? - Yeah.
看起来更像土豆泥啊
It looks a bit more like mashed potatoes.
瞅 发明小屋有感恩节挥泪甩卖活动
Look, big Thanksgiving sale at the gizmo hut.
他们卖的笔记本只有四十九块 太便宜了
They're selling mytabs for $49? That's awesome!
可不是嘛 但我们需要早点儿去排队
I know! But we have to get in line early.
因为他们只甩卖十个
Because they'll only have 10 of these at that price.
难道我们要在感恩节那天去排队吗
So we have to wait in line on Thanksgiving day?
是啊 甩卖从午夜开始
Yes, the sale starts at midnight.
他们这不是折腾人嘛
Why did they have to make it so hard?
我们只想赞美一下
All we wanna do is celebrate.
感恩节的真谛
The true meaning of Thanksgiving...
白菜价买下电子产品
Buying electronics at terrific prices.
可不是嘛
I'm saying.
火鸡
Turkey.
为什么我每次过来都是你来开门
Why do you always answer the door when I come over?
那不如你就别过来了 我也不用过来给你开门了
How about you stop coming over and I'll stop answering the door?
嗨 达布尼太太
Hi, Mrs. Dabney.
艾米 我请教个问题
Amy, I have a question for you.
你知道哪有卖小一点儿的火鸡吗
Do you know where I can get a small Turkey for one?
因为今年只有我一个人
It's just me this year.
噢 是吗 达布尼先生呢
Oh, well, where's Mr. Dabney?
你没听说吗 我和那家伙离婚了
Didn't you hear? I divorced his sorry butt.
噢 对此我深表同情
Oh, I'm so sorry to hear that.
我不难过 我们在一起就是个悲剧
I'm not. We were just making each other miserable.
如今我可以像平常一样活泼开朗了
Now I can be the happy-go-lucky person I always was.
活泼开朗
You are?
我是说 是说 你当然可以了
I mean... I mean, you can.
活泼开朗吗
You are?
总之 我只能
So anyway, I'll be eating.
独守空房 撕咬小火鸡了
That tiny Turkey in that big empty house,
茕茕孑立 形影相吊
All alone, by myself,
就寡人一人
Just me.
挺好的 就当是为了圣诞节预演了
Well, it'll be good practice for Christmas.
不送
After you.
达布尼太太 您愿意
Mrs. Dabney, would you like to...
达布尼太太 您愿意和我们一起
Mrs. Dabney, would you like to join us.
吃感恩节晚宴吗
For Thanksgiving dinner?
这个嘛 这个情况发生的太突然了
Well, this is coming out of nowhere.
我要去查查我的安排计划
I'll have to check my schedule.
不用送了
Bye now.
你这是何苦呢
Why did you do that?
我这是怜悯仁慈
I was being gracious.
做一个友好的邻居
And I was being neighborly.
好吧 但是记住 圣诞节就别这么好客了
All right, well, that better end by Christmas.
嘿 老妈 手里拿的什么东西
Hey, mom, what you got there?
晚宴的菜单
It's the menu for Thanksgiving.
说到感恩节
Talk about great timing.
我自愿为您下厨的时候打下手
Because I was gonna volunteer to help you cook.
PJ啊 你太贴心了 但我还是想让泰迪帮忙
P.J., that is so sweet, but actually I was gonna ask Teddy.
老妈啊 泰迪没功夫的
Mom, Teddy does not have time.
她沉浸在自己的小世界里
She is off in her own little world.
洋娃娃啊 小马驹啊
With the dolls and the horses.
还有漂亮的衣服
And the dress-up.
她不是七岁小孩 你知道这点吧
You do know she's not seven, right?
先不管了 让我看看菜单
Whatever. Let me see the list.
好了 我稍微标注一下
Okay, I'm just gonna put a little check.
我想做的菜品
Next to the things I like to cook.
这个 这个 噢 还有这个
Yeah, yes. Ooh, definitely.
这个 这个 这个 这个
Oh oh oh oh, yeah.
儿子 你除了面包卷 剩下的全画上了
Honey, you checked everything but the rolls.
噢 没错 抱歉 “面包圈”
Oh, right, sorry. "rolls."
好吧 好吧 这些都归你
Okay, fine, you can cook all that other stuff,
但是火鸡必须归我
But I am definitely cooking the Turkey.
等等 单子上没有火鸡啊
Wait, that wasn't on the list.
是啊 我以为这是众所周知的
Well, I thought it was obvious.
我全把注意力放在配菜上了 却忘了主菜
I got bogged down on the side dishes, lost my focus.
情况如何
So how did it go?
有些不妙
I've got some bad news.
怎么了
What?
她只做一道菜
She's making one dish.
老天保佑是西兰花 老天保佑是西兰花
Please say broccoli. Please say broccoli.
它的别名是吐绶鸡
It rhymes with schmurkey.
是火鸡
It's Turkey.
-嘿 大伙看看 爷爷来了 -嘿
- Hey, everybody, grandpa's here. - Hey!
成了 成了 你们都长这么大了 此处省去一万字
Yeah yeah, my, how you've grown. Blah blah blah.
您肯定还没见过查莉吧
I don't believe you've met Charlie.
干嘛把他打扮成女孩
Now why is he dressed like a girl?
因为她就是个女孩
Well, because she is a girl.
没错 查莉是夏洛特的简称
Yes, Charlie is short for Charlotte.
那为什么不叫夏莉
Then why isn't she called Sharlie?
说真的 我真搞不懂
Seriously, I don't get it.
你给一个姑娘起了一个小子的名字 他应该叫泰迪
You give the girls boys' names. He should be Teddy,
他应该叫查莉 而她应该叫PJ
He should be Charlie, and she should be P.J.
我们不会再给孩子重起名字了 爹啊
We're not renaming the kids, dad.
好消息啊 我查了查安排计划
Good news. I checked my schedule,
看来在感恩节我还是有空档的
And it turns out I am available on Thanksgiving.
好吧 搞什么 谁忘了关门了
All right, really? Who left the door open?
达布尼夫人 这是我岳父大人 弗兰克·邓肯
Mrs. Dabney, this is my father-in-law Frank Duncan.
弗兰克 这位是埃斯特尔·达布尼
Frank, Estelle Dabney.
老鲍 能不能请你过来一下
Bob, I was wondering if you could come over.
看看我的垃圾处理机
And look at my garbage disposal.
-好像有些问题 -噢 我来吧
- It's not working right. - Oh, I'll do it.
毕竟我干了三十年的水管工
Had my own plumbing business for 30 years.
管道这种事情 是男人的活儿
Plumbing, now that's a man's job.
如果你想抓蝴蝶了
You want someone to catch a butterfly,
叫我儿子吧
Call my son.
走吧
Let's go.
好耶 我们是九号十号
Yes, we're numbers nine and 10!
-你是九号 俺是十号 -是啊
- You're nine and I'm 10? - Yeah.
为什么俺不是九号
Why don't I get to be nine?
有什么区别吗 我们都有份
What difference does it make? We're both getting mytabs.
那让俺来九号
Then I'm nine.
噢 这下好了 看来我这一整天都要排在
Oh, great, I gotta spend the rest of the day in line.
你们两个废物后面
Behind you two losers.
看看 看看 看看
Well well well,
这不是卡尔吗 那个混蛋邻居
If it isn't Karl, the neighborhood jerk.
如果你也奔着笔记本来的
If you were planning on getting a mytab,
那你就悲剧了 因为你是十一号
You're out of luck. You're number 11.
除非我排你前面
Not if I outrun you.
当我把笔记本拿到手后 我就去废物大本营网站
And when I get my mytab, I'm gonna go online to the losers site.
然后在你的主页上留言
And post something on your loser page.
就写 “嘿 废物”
That says, "hey, loser!"
今天不好熬啊
This is gonna be a long day.
对不起了 卡尔 我要拉起这面无形的墙
Excuse me, Karl. I'm gonna zip up the invisible wall now.
这样我就不用听你废话了
So we don't have to listen to you.
你还是能听到我的
You can still hear me.
我知道你能
I know you can.
嘿 无形墙 愚蠢之极
Hey, invisible walls... stupid.
抱歉 你说啥
I'm sorry, what?
小泰 你先走吧 赶回去吃感恩节晚宴
T, you should get going so you can make it home for your Thanksgiving dinner.
对 没错 好吧 我四点赶回来 再换你去吃
Yeah, you're right. Well, I'll be back at 4:00 so you can go to your dinner.
-一会见 -一会见
- See ya. - See ya.
嘿 艾薇姐
Hey, Ivy,
现在泰迪走了
Now that Teddy's gone,
我终于可以澄清一下 我不是混蛋
I can finally admit that I'm not really a jerk.
我只是一个太害怕去承认
I'm just a vulnerable kid who's too scared to admit.
自己也需要朋友的脆弱小孩
That he needs a friend.
噢 真的吗
Oh, really?
才怪 我就是个混蛋 你个蠢货
No, I'm a jerk. Loser!
没说错 难熬的一天
Yep, a real long day.
噢 天啊 太怪了
Oh, man, this is just weird.
-什么怪 -爷爷
- What is? - Grandpa.
他看起来很开心
He seems happy.
让人心神不宁啊
It's very unsettling.
躲猫猫 我看见你啦
Peek-a-boo, I see you.
躲猫猫
Peek-a-boo.
好了 咱俩过去 看看他是否正常
All right, you know what? We'd better go make sure he's okay.
开始啦 我要抓到你
Here we go. I'm gonna get ya!
我来啦 呜
Here he comes. Whooo!
噢 她真是萌死了
Oh, she's a cutie pie!
盖比 当你也这么大的时候 同样有够萌
And you were cute, too, when you were at that age, Gabe. Boop.
祝大家 感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving, everyone!
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving.
她居然也怪怪的
She's acting weird, too?
好吧 出问题了
Okay, something's not right.
多么美好的一天啊
This is such a wonderful day.
我要感谢的人有很多
I have so much to be thankful for.
感谢谁
Like what?
这个嘛 我要感谢
Well, I am thankful.
这位出现在我生命里的新白马王子
That I have a new man in my life.
而我要感谢 我就是那白马王子
And I am thankful to be that man.
呃 你俩现在如胶似漆了
Um... So you two are together now?
说对了
That's right.
就在弗兰克疏通了我的管道之后
After Frank unclogged my disposal...
他也疏通了我的心灵
He unclogged my heart.
看来我要借宿于此
So it looks like I'll be sticking around.
一段时间了
For a while.
说不准呢 盖比 有朝一日
And who knows, Gabe? Someday soon,
你会管我叫奶奶的
You might be calling me grandma.
盖比 让我们去去就回
Gabe, let's go for a catch.
-什么 -快去外面
- A what? - Just go outside.
好了 咱们怎么办
All right, what are we gonna do?
还能怎么办 拆散这对鸳鸯
There's only one thing we can do. We gotta split 'em up.
噢 作孽啊
Oh, that sounds evil.
我喜欢
I like it.
嘿 知道吗
Hey, you know what?
我们所做的就是让他们了解对方
All we have to do is just help them to get to know each other.
也就是说 只要了解对方后
I mean, once we do that...
就会讨厌对方的
Then they'll hate each other.
-正解 -耶
- Exactly. - Yeah!
等等 先等一下 我们真要这么干吗
Wait wait wait. Should we do this?
他们已经日薄西山了 就不能让他们再幸福一回吗
They are older people. This may be their last chance at happiness.
你是说你后妈的幸福生活吗
You mean your new mom's last chance at happiness?
好吧 必须拆散他们
Yeah, they're going down.
-怎么了 -儿子 我把火鸡烤缩水了
- What happened? - Honey, I shrunk the Turkey.
噢 不会吧 你肯定是用了飘悬焙烧法
Oh no, you must have flash roasted it.
飘悬焙烧法 什么东西
Flash roasted? What's that?
这个嘛 有些复杂
Well, it's complicated.
只有在填充料过多和火候太大同时发生时
It's what happens when you simultaneously.
才会出现这种情况
Over-breast and under-roast.
简而言之 任何东西都会被缩水
Put simply, it shrinks everything.
-即使是骨头 -特别是骨头
- Even the bones? - Especially the bones.
PJ 我们该怎么办啊
P.J., what are we gonna do?
好吧 让我仔细想想
Well, I'm just thinking on my feet here,
-我们有口油炸锅 -是啊 怎么了
- But we do have a deep fryer. - Yeah, so?
那我们就油炸火鸡 晚餐就可以在九十分钟内搞定
So if we deep fry a Turkey, dinner could be ready in 90 minutes.
我们去哪再找一只火鸡
Where are we gonna get another bird on Thanksgiving?
我有只备用的火鸡放在车库了
I have a spare Turkey in the garage.
你怎么会有备用的火鸡在车库里
Why do you have a spare Turkey in the garage?
为什么你没有备用的火鸡在车库里
Why don't you have a spare Turkey in the garage?
-快去拿 -好的
- Go get it. - Okay.
嘿 老妈 还有多久才能开饭
Hey, mom, are we gonna eat soon?
因为大家都快饿死了
'cause everyone's really hungry.
而且希望能在四点之前吃完
And would love to be done by 4:00.
说实话 晚餐被推迟了
Actually, dinner has been delayed.
PJ用了飘悬焙烧法
P.J. Flash roasted the Turkey.
导致我们要重头来过
And now we have to start all over.
艾薇 嗨 是我
Ivy, hi, it's me.
听着 我老妈搞砸了火鸡
Listen, my mom ruined the Turkey.
还嫁祸于PJ
And blamed it on my brother,
所以我晚点回去
So I'm gonna be late.
好了 别慌 别慌
Yeah, no, okay. Don't worry, though.
我会想办法的 你坚守住阵地
I'll think of something. Just... you stay in line.
我尽快赶到 好的
I'll be there as soon as I can. Okay.
老妈 噢 老妈啊
Mom, oh... mom,
我头疼
I have a headache.
哇 看来我应该回房休息一下
Wow. So maybe I should rest in my room for a bit.
你可能两个小时都看不见我 因为你懂得
So if you don't see me for, like, two hours or so just remember,
我在房间里呢
I'm in my room.
闺女啊 你可能是饿了
Well, honey, you're probably hungry.
给你 先拿迷你版火鸡垫垫肚子
Here, nibble on the flash Turkey.
算了 我还是回房间吧
Yeah, I'll be in my room.
如果我把你煮了 你能膨胀回来吗
If I boil you, will you plump back up?
你和谁说话呢
Who are you talking to?
迷你火鸡
The mini Turkey.
埃斯特尔 你让我重获新生
Estelle, you make me feel like a new man.
-汪 -喵
- Woof! - Meow.
嘿 知道吗 我知道一种特别好玩的游戏
Hey, you know what? I got a really fun game.
叫做 别学兽叫
Called let's not make animal sounds.
这么说来 达布尼夫人
So, Mrs. Dabney...
噢 盖比 小乖乖 别这么见外
Oh, Gabe, baby, why so formal?
直接叫我婆婆 叫我奶奶更好了
Call me Nana. Or better yet gam-gam.
这么说来 哈哈 奶奶
So, ha ha ha, gam-gam...
你刚才学的猫叫很是有趣
It's interesting that you meowed,
因为我们都知道你很爱你的小猫咪们
Because we know how much you love your Cat caboodle.
我爸可不喜欢猫 对吧 爸
And dad doesn't like cats at all. Isn't that right, dad?
-讨厌猫 -那就不留一只猫
- Hate 'em. - Then caboodle's gone.
但你爱你的猫 胜过任何事情
But you love that Cat more than anything.
-本来我也是这么想的 -噢
- I thought I did. - Oh.
嘿 你知道我爸在睡觉时鼾声雷动吗
Hey, did you know my dad snores so loud,
鼾声能掀翻屋顶
He rattles the whole house?
那太好了 我前夫睡觉特别安静
Good, Mr. Dabney was one of those silent sleepers.
至少这个呼噜声
At least with a snorer,
可以让我知道这个屋子里有个纯爷们
You know there's a man in the house.
我希望这个纯爷们可以久居于此
And I hope he's there for a long time.
我也是
Me too.
-汪 -喵
- Woof. - Meow.
嘿 情况如何了 大家真的都饿了
Hey, how we doing out here? Everyone's really hungry.
应该会在九十分钟内搞定
Dinner should be ready in 90 minutes.
你能提点速吗
You think you could speed it up?
弗兰克爷爷一直在达布尼夫人的后背上画心形
Grandpa Frank keeps tracing finger hearts on Mrs. Dabney's back.
那我应该可以先弄点小三明治给他们
I guess I could whip up some little sandwiches.
-看好了火鸡 成吗 -好啊 没问题
- Watch the bird, okay? - Yeah, sure.
我可以看着火鸡提速两倍
I'm gonna watch it cook twice as fast.
查莉 你要吃你的三明治了吗
Charlie, are you gonna eat your sandwich?
-是 -好吧 我能咬一小口吗
- Yes. - Well, can I have just a bite?
不 爸爸
No, daddy.
我给你买娃娃
I'll buy you a doll.
好了 大家
Okay, everyone,
晚饭十分钟内搞定
Dinner will be ready in 10 minutes.
不对吧 火鸡还要再做一个小时呢
No, it won't. The Turkey's gotta cook for another hour.
那你就错了 我加大了火候
That's where you're wrong. I turned up the heat.
-你什么 -加大火候啊 节省了一半时间
- You did what? - Turned up the heat, cut the cooking time in half.
你不能这样 如果油太热了 那火鸡就有可能
You can't do that. If the oil gets too hot, then the Turkey might...
爆炸
Explode.
噢 看那火鸡飞得多高多远
Oh, look at that Turkey go!
噢 不要啊 掉下来了
Oh no, it's coming back down.
-呜 呜 呜 -不 不 不
- Whoa whoa whoa! - No no no!
好了 艾薇 我正赶过去呢
Okay, Ivy, I'm on my way.
好的 再见
Yeah, see ya.
感觉怎么样了 宝贝
How you feeling, sweetie?
我这是怎么了
What happened to me again?
火鸡从天而降 砸到了你
Turkey fell out of the sky on you.
但是火鸡不会飞啊 对吧
But turkeys can't fly. Can they?
不能飞 在动画片里可以飞
No, I guess in cartoons they can.
噢 我爱看动画片
Oh, I like cartoons.
好了 大家
Okay, everybody.
刚从自动售货机里出来的
Fresh from the vending machine.
-感恩节快乐 -好吧 至少还有火鸡
- Happy Thanksgiving. - Well, at least they're Turkey.
或者 “可能含有火鸡”
Or "may contain Turkey."
嘿 亲爱的 真对不起
Hey, honey, I'm sorry.
你又要在医院里吃火鸡三明治了
You gotta eat Turkey sandwiches in the hospital again.
我知道这并不是你所期望的
I know this isn't the Thanksgiving you wanted.
说实话 的确不是
Well, it's not.
但你知道吗 至少我们还在一起
But you know what? We're all together.
泰迪无大碍
Teddy's okay.
正是我所要感谢的
And that is what I'm thankful for.
是啊 嘿 知道吗
Yeah. Hey, you know what?
我要感谢在场的每一个人
I am thankful for everybody in this room.
-我也是 -我也是
- Me too. - Me too.
我要感谢212房的病人 给我订了冰激凌
I'm thankful that the patient in room 212 ordered ice cream.
我很想知道那对鸳鸯在干什么
I wonder how the lovebirds are doing.
你不能这么和我说话
You can't talk to me that way.
我爱怎么和你说就怎么说 蠢蛋
I can talk to you any way I want, dimwit.
步入正轨了
That sounds promising.
嘿 怎么了
Hey, what's going on?
他是个蠢蛋
He's an idiot.
她是包租婆
She's a battleaxe.
这个 我们知道 你俩怎么了
Yeah, we knew that, but what happened?
我俩独处了一个小时
We spent an hour alone together.
我这辈子最长的一个小时
Longest hour of my life.
这么说来你俩掰了
So you two aren't a couple anymore?
掰了 一刀两断
No, we are not.
亏我当初还想和你一起回亚历桑那定居
And to think, I was gonna move to Arizona with you.
你说啥
Say what now?
等等 等等 别这么急着下决定
Wait wait. There's still time.
你俩可以渡过难关的 我是说 你俩天生一对
You guys can work this out. I mean, you're perfect for each other.
-噢 -等等 等等 回来啊
- Oh! - Wait wait, come back!
奶奶啊
Gam-gam!
好了 查莉 又是一年的邓肯家感恩节
Well, Charlie, another Duncan family Thanksgiving.
就这么过去了
Has come and gone.
好消息是邓肯爷爷
The good news is grandpa Duncan.
打道回府了
Has also come and gone.
嘿 泰迪 你觉着这个怎么样
Hey, Teddy, tell me what you think about this.
“亲爱的达布尼夫人”
"Dear Mrs. Dabney,"
我对于咱俩之间的不愉快而感到抱歉 请原谅我
I'm sorry for our ugly words. Please forgive me.
请火速卖掉你的房子 搬到凤凰城来
Sell your house and move to Phoenix immediately.
不要急着给我打电话 给我个惊喜
Do not call first. Just surprise me.
“永远爱你的 爷爷”
"Forever yours, grandpa."
我感觉你应该署名 “弗兰克”
I think you'd sign it "Frank."
噢 对啊 太好了 我可以这么写
Oh, yeah, that's good. I could use that.
总之 鉴于我们还没有吃到一顿感恩节晚宴
Anyway, since we never got a Thanksgiving dinner,
PJ打算再油炸一只火鸡
P.J. Is about to deep fry another Turkey.
所以为了保证人身安全
So just to be on the safe side.
祝我好运吧 查莉
Wish me good luck, Charlie.
这简直就是我人生中
That was the worst shopping experience.
-最糟糕的购物了 -我也是
- Of my life. - Mine too.
我是说 我听说过这里的销售相当野蛮
I mean, I heard those sales were brutal,
但我并没料到能野蛮到这种地步
But I didn't know they were this bad.
而且最后的一台笔记本离我们近在咫尺
And we were so close to getting that last mytab.
然后那怪物冲进来了
Then that monster came in.
我们像布娃娃一样被扔到了一边
And started throwing us around like ragdolls.
这里发生了什么
What just happened in there?
卡尔 你哭了
Karl, are you crying?
有人踩我脖子上了
Somebody stepped on my neck.
走吧
C'mon.
难道为了一台破笔记本 值得这样摧残我们吗
And is it really worth treating people like this to get a stupid mytab?
值得
Yes.